https://www.bestsharpeningstones.com/privacy.php

100%
SATISFACTION
GUARANTEED!
Get your order
FAST!
Privacy Policy
We understand the importance of privacy to our customers and visitors to our site. We take your privacy seriously and we are committed to protecting it. Please take a moment to review our Privacy Policy.
Collection of Information
We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with anyone for their promotional use. We do not share any information with marketing companies. The information you provide is used only to process your order or answer questions you have submitted to us.
Spam
We will never send spam or unsolicited emails. The only emails you will receive from us will be in direct response to an order you have placed such as a tracking number email or a copy of your invoice.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
We do not use cookie or tracking technology. Personal information is not collected via cookies and other tracking technology.
Distribution of Information
We do not distribute your information to anyone; however, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention. We may do so when: (1) protecting against potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (2) investigating fraud which has already taken place.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential, have access to this information.
Questions or Comments
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy please contact us.
